Finding Aid for Claude Thomas Stoner Photographs and Papers 1870s-1977
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Classified Photographs
  - Manistee & North Eastern
    - Station, Traverse City, Mich., early 1890s, [MNE36-37 (Box 1)
      (formerly FPM1-2)
    - Engine 11 and log train, [MNE38] (Box 1)
    - Engine 10, [MNE39] (Box 1)
    - Engine 7 and passenger train, Traverse City, Mich. circa 1900s, [MNE40] (Box 1)
    - Engine 14 and passenger train, Traverse City, Mich., [MNE41] (Box 1)
    - Engine 481, [MNE42] (Box 1)
    - Engine 12, [MNE43] (Box 1)
    - Station, Onekama, Mich. 1917, [MNE44] (Box 1)
    - Engine 19 and train, Camp Grayling, Mich., [MNE45] (Box 1)
    - Depot, Sigma, Mich., [MNE46] (Box 1)
    - Engine 11, work train, and Shovel no. 1 circa 1913, [MNE47] (Box 1)
    - Engine 3 and mixed train, Honor branch circa 1914, [MNE48] (Box 1)
    - Engine 8 and freight train, early 1900s, [MNE49] (Box 1)
  - Mason & Oceana, Butters Peters & Co., Buttersville, Mich.
    (Code MO)
    - Engine 2, [MO1] (Box 1)
    - Butters & Peters mill, Buttersville, Mich., with Shay engine and log train, [MO2] (Box 1)
    - Engines Peggy and Shay near Peachville, Mich., [MO3] (Box 1)
    - Engine Mogul, [MO4-5] (Box 1)
    - Engine 5, [MO6] (Box 1)
    - Engine 1 and passenger car circa 1905, [MO7] (Box 1)
    - Engine 7, [MO8] (Box 1)
    - Engine 1, [MO9] (Box 1)
  - Mineral Range
    (Code MR)
    - Engine 190 and passenger train, [MR1] (Box 1)
    - Engine 193, [MR2] (Box 1)
  - Munising Railway
    (Code MRY)
    - Engine 2, builder's photo, [MRY1] (Box 1)
    - Engine 3 with pilot plow, [MRY2] (Box 1)
  - Michigan Southern & Northern Indiana
    (Code MS)
    - [Moved], [MS1 changed to LSMS32] (Box 1)
    - Engine 15, [MS2] (Box 1)
  - Marquette & Southeastern
    (Code MSE)
    - Engine 32, [MSE1] (Box 1)
    - Engine 36, [MSE2] (Box 1)
  - Mount Washington Cog Railway
    (Code MW)
    - Engine 1, [MW1] (Box 1)
    - Engine 1 with Engine 8 in background, [MW2] (Box 1)
    - Engine 8, [MW3-4] (Box 1)
    - Engine 8 climbing mountain, [MW5-6] (Box 1)
    - Switch in cog railway track, [MW7] (Box 1)
    - Trains at Base Station 1878, [MW8] (Box 1)
    - Climbing the mountain circa 1870, [MW9] (Box 1)
    - Early engine on Jacob's Ladder, [MW10] (Box 1)
  - Nashville & Chattanooga
    (Code NC)
    - Depot, car shops, repair shops, and yard, Nashville, Tenn., during Civil War, [NC1] (Box 1)
  - Northern Michigan Traction Co., Manistee, Mich. (Box 1)
    (Code NMT)
    - Car 18, [NMT1] (Box 1)
    - Six trailers and switching motor, [NMT2] (Box 1)
    - Three trailers, [NMT3] (Box 1)
    - Four-wheel open car, [NMT4] (Box 1)
    - Four-wheel closed car, [NMT5] (Box 1)
  - Nahma & Northern, Bay de Noquet Lumber Co., Nahma, Mich.
    (Code NN)
    - Engine 5, Nahma Junction, Mich. 1951, [NN1] (Box 1)
  - Cincinnati Northern
    (Code NOR)
    - Passenger train at water tank and coal dock, Hudson, Mich., [NOR1] (Box 1)
    - Engine taking water during flood, Hudson, Mich., [NOR2] (Box 1)
  - Norfolk & Western
    (Code NW)
    - Engine 1215 Columbus, Ohio 1954, [NW1-3] (Box 1)
    - Engine 212, Columbus, Ohio 1954, [NW4-5] (Box 1)
    - Wrecker, Columbus, Ohio 1954, [NW6] (Box 1)
  - New York Central
    (Code NYC)
    - Engine 5344 Ann Arbor, Mich. 1942, [NYC1-3] (Box 1)
    - Engine 2045 and oil train, Dexter, Mich. 1943, [NYC4] (Box 1)
    - Engine 2399 Dexter, Mich. 1943, [NYC5] (Box 1)
    - Engine 2000 Dexter, Mich. 1943, [NYC6] (Box 1)
    - Express train 139, Albion, Mich. 1937, [NYC7] (Box 1)
    - Double head passenger train taking water at track pan, Chelsea, Mich. 1943, [NYC8] (Box 1)
    - Engine 5353 and express train at track pan, Chelsea, Mich. 1948, [NYC9] (Box 1)
    - Mercury taking water at track pan, Chelsea, Mich. 1943, [NYC10] (Box 1)
    - Passenger train near Albion, Mich. 1937, [NYC11] (Box 1)
    - Trains at station, Ann Arbor, Mich. 1942, [NYC12] (Box 1)
    - Engine 2218 wrecked at depot, Ann Arbor, Mich. 1940, [NYC13-15] (Box 1)
    - Track pan, Marshall, Mich. 1937, [NYC16] (Box 1)
    - Tank, pump house, and track pan, Marshall, Mich. 1937, [NYC17] (Box 1)
    - Engine 1028 Dexter, Mich. 1945, [NYC18] (Box 1)
      (2 different negatives, only one is printed)
    - Engine 2360 and freight train at track pan, Chelsea, Mich. 1949, [NYC19] (Box 1)
    - Engine 2228 and Diesel engine 683, Dexter, Mich. 1949, [NYC20-21] (Box 1)
    - Diesel engine 683 1949, [NYC22] (Box 1)
    - Engine 2228 and freight train east of Dexter, Mich. 1949, [NYC23] (Box 1)
    - Engine 5247 and passenger train, Dexter, Mich 1949, [NYC24] (Box 1)
    - Engine 6896, [NYC25] (Box 1)
    - Motor train M-205, Dexter, Mich 1950, [NYC26] (Box 1)
    - Budd RDC rail car, Jackson, Mich. 1952, [NYC27-28] (Box 1)
    - Passenger train at depot, Jackson, Mich. 1952, [NYC29] (Box 1)
    - Cleveland, Cincinnati, Chicago & St. Louis Engine 6510, [NYC30] (Box 1)
    - Mill Creek bridge, Dexter, Mich. 1948, [NYC31] (Box 1)
    - New York Central & Hudson River Engine 870, [NYC32] (Box 1)
    - New York Central & Hudson River Engine 908, [NYC33] (Box 1)
    - Motor car M-205 and train at Ypsilanti, Mich., [NYC34] (Box 1)
    - Engine 5284 Ann Arbor, Mich. 1951, [NYC35] (Box 1)
    - New York Central & Hudson River Engine 1(?) Albany, N.Y. 1872, [NYC36] (Box 1)
    - New York Central & Hudson River Engine 999 at Worlds' Fair, [NYC37] (Box 1)
    - Lake Shore & Michigan Southern station, Saline, Mich. 1962, [NYC38] (Box 1)
    - U.S. Railroad Administration Engine 5155, [NYC39] (Box 1)
    - Mercury taking water, Four Mile Lake, Mich., [NYC40] (Box 1)
    - Engine 1896, [NYC41] (Box 1)
    - Depot, Dexter, Mich. circa 1950, [NYC42] (Box 1)
    - Passenger train and depot, Dexter, Mich., Railroad centennial 1941, [NYC43] (Box 1)
    - Engine 5429 Mercury, east of Ann Arbor, Mich. 1940s, [NYC44] (Box 1)
    - Freight train at track pan, Chelsea, Mich., [NYC45] (Box 1)
      (negative marked NYC15)
    - Engine 5347 and passenger train taking water, [NYC46] (Box 1)
      (negative marked NYC13)
    - Passenger train at track pan, Chelsea, Mich. 1948, [NYC47] (Box 1)
      (negative marked NYC14]
  - Owosso & Corunna Traction Co.
    (Code OCT)
    - Baggage and passenger car, [OCT1] (Box 1)
  - Oshawa Railway
    (Code OR)
    - Motor 44, Oshawa, Ont. 1956, [OR1] (Box 1)
  - Passes
    (Code P)
    - Toledo Ann Arbor & North Michigan (Box 2)
      - 1895, [P1] (Box 2)
    - Ann Arbor Railroad
      - 1896, [P2] (Box 2)
      - 1898, [P3] (Box 2)
      - 1902, [P4] (Box 2)
    - Ann Arbor Railroad and Detroit, Toledo & Ironton Railway
      - 1907, [P5] (Box 2)
      - 1908, [P6] (Box 2)
    - Ann Arbor Railroad
      - 1909, [P7] (Box 2)
      - 1912, [P8] (Box 2)
      - 1914, [P9] (Box 2)
    - Detroit, Lansing & Northern
      - 1889, [P10] (Box 2)
    - Chicago & West Michigan and Detroit, Lansing & Northern
      - 1891, [P11] (Box 2)
      - 1892, [P12] (Box 2)
    - Flint & Pere Marquette
      - 1873, [P13] (Box 2)
      - 1890, [P14a] (Box 2)
      - 1890 verso, [P14b] (Box 2)
      - 1891, [P15] (Box 2)
      - 1895, [P16a] (Box 2)
      - 1895 verso, [P16b] (Box 2)
    - Saginaw Valley and St. Louis
      - 1874, [P17] (Box 2)
    - Flint & Pere Marquette
      - 1898, [P18] (Box 2)
    - Lake Shore & Michigan Southern
      - 1887, [P19] (Box 2)
    - Michigan Air Line Railroad
      - 1871, [P20a] (Box 2)
      - 1871 verso, [P20b] (Box 2)
    - Michigan Central
      - 1873, [P21] (Box 2)
      - 1886, [P22] (Box 2)
      - 1891, [P23] (Box 2)
      - 1899, [P24] (Box 2)
    - Manistee & North Eastern
      - 1918, [P25] (Box 2)
    - Cincinnati, Jackson & Mackinaw
      - 1897, [P26] (Box 2)
    - New York Central Sleeping Car Co.
      - 1886, [P27] (Box 2)
    - Wagner Palace Car Co.
      - 1888, [P28] (Box 2)
      - 1894, [P29] (Box 2)
    - Pullman's Palace Car Co.
      - 1899, [P30] (Box 2)
    - Western Union Telegraph Co.
      - 1899, [P31] (Box 2)
    - American Telegraph Co.
      - 1874, [P32] (Box 2)
    - Saginaw Street Railroad Co.
      - 1875, [P33] (Box 2)
    - Detroit & Bay City
      - 1873, [P34] (Box 2)
    - Fort Wayne, Jackson & Saginaw
      - 1873, [P35] (Box 2)
    - Michigan Central
      - 1881, [P36] (Box 2)
    - Grand Rapids & Indiana
      - 1899, [P37] (Box 2)
    - Chicago & Michigan Lake Shore
      - 1873, [P38] (Box 2)
    - Chicago, Saginaw & Canada
      - 1876, [P39] (Box 2)
    - Grand Rapids, Newaygo & Lake Shore
      - 1876, [P40] (Box 2)
    - Detroit, Lansing & Lake Michigan
      - 1873, [P41] (Box 2)
    - Detroit, Lansing & Northern
      - 1880, [P42] (Box 2)
    - Detroit, Grand Rapids & Western
      - 1898, [P43] (Box 2)
    - Chicago & West Michigan and Detroit, Grand Rapids & Western
      - 1899, [P44] (Box 2)
    - Toledo Ann Arbor & North Michigan
      - 1889, [P45a] (Box 2)
      - 1889 verso, [P45b] (Box 2)
    - Saginaw River Steamboat Line
      - 1879, [P46] (Box 2)
    - River Line Steamers
      - 1889, [P47] (Box 2)
    - Manistee & North Eastern
      - 1921, [P48] (Box 2)
    - Traverse City, Leelanau & Manistique
      - 1918, [P49] (Box 2)
    - Chicago & West Michigan
      - 1888, [P50] (Box 2)
    - Grand Rapids & Indiana
      - 1894, [P51] (Box 2)
    - Michigan Central
      - 1894, [P52] (Box 2)
    - St. Clair Tunnel Co.
      - 1894, [P53] (Box 2)
    - Saginaw, Tuscola & Huron
      - 1894, [P54] (Box 2)
    - Toledo & Western
      - 1925, [P55] (Box 2)
    - Toledo & Ann Arbor
      - 1879, [P56] (Box 2)
    - Detroit, Hillsdale & Indiana and Detroit, Eel River & Illinois
      - 1873, [P57] (Box 2)
    - Detroit, Hillsdale & South Western
      - 1976, [P58] (Box 2)
    - Detroit & Milwaukee
      - 1873, [P59] (Box 2)
    - Flint & Pere Marquette
      - 1880, [P60a] (Box 2)
      - 1880 verso, [P60b] (Box 2)
      - 1889 verso, [P61] (Box 2)
    - Marquette, Houghton & Ontonagon
      - 1878, [P62] (Box 2)
    - Northwestern Grand Trunk and Chicago & Northeastern
      - 1880, [P63] (Box 2)
    - Port Huron & Lake Michigan
      - 1873, [P64] (Box 2)
    - Saginaw Valley & St. Louis
      - 1876, [P65] (Box 2)
    - Western Union Telegraph Co.
      - 1882, [P66] (Box 2)
    - Manistee & Grand Rapids
      - 1910, [P67] (Box 2)
    - Pere Marquette Line Steamers
      - 1910, [P68] (Box 2)
  - Pere Marquette
    (Code PM)
    - Depot and freight house, Howell, Mich. 1936, [PM1] (Box 2)
    - Reverse curve, Howell, Mich. 1937, [PM2] (Box 2)
    - Interlocker tower, Annpere, Mich. 1936, [PM3] (Box 2)
    - Engine 714 and passenger train, Howell, Mich. 1937, [PM4] (Box 2)
    - Engine 1212, Howell, Mich. 1937, [PM5] (Box 2)
    - Interlocker tower, Annpere, Mich. 1936, [PM6] (Box 2)
    - Wreck, Annpere, Mich. 1908, [PM7] (Box 2)
      no negative
    - Engine 249, [PM8] (Box 2)
    - Engine 190 and passenger train, [PM9] (Box 2)
    - High bridge, Manistee River, Mich. circa 1910, [PM10] (Box 2)
    - Engine 4, Windsor, Ont. 1922, [PM11] (Box 2)
    - Engine 801, Walkerville, Ont. 1921, [PM12] (Box 2)
    - Engine 809, Walkerville, Ont. 1921, [PM13] (Box 2)
    - Engine 419, [PM14] (Box 2)
    - Engine 91, [PM15] (Box 2)
    - Engine 233, Stanton, Mich. 1910, [PM16] (Box 2)
    - Engine 205 at station, Coral, Mich. 1910, [PM17] (Box 2)
    - Engine 375, [PM18] (Box 2)
    - Roundhouse, Traverse City, Mich. circa 1910, [PM19] (Box 2)
    - Engine 254, [PM20] (Box 2)
    - Engine 718, [PM21] (Box 2)
    - Engine 1046 in yard, Traverse City, Mich., [PM22] (Box 2)
    - Engine 375, [PM23] (Box 2)
    - Engine 425, Sigma, Mich. circa 1910, [PM24] (Box 2)
    - Engine 720, [PM25] (Box 2)
    - Engine 1199, [PM26] (Box 2)
    - Old depot, South Lyon, Mich., [PM27] (Box 2)
    - New depot, South Lyon, Mich., [PM28] (Box 2)
    - Wreck, Salem, Mich. 1907, [PM29] (Box 2)
    - Engine 7 and passenger train near Fremont, Mich. circa 1912, [PM30] (Box 2)
    - Engine 213 1940, [PM31] (Box 2)
    - Engine 1115, [PM32] (Box 2)
    - Engine 7, [PM33] (Box 2)
    - Engine 61 and train, Bendon, Mich., [PM34] (Box 2)
    - Engine 70 and crew, [PM35] (Box 2)
    - Engine 192 and passenger train, Charlevoix, Mich., [PM36] (Box 2)
    - Wreck south of Petoskey, Mich. 1912, [PM37] (Box 2)
    - Wreck near Traverse City, Mich. 1919, [PM38-39] (Box 2)
    - Engine 20 and train at station, Grand Ledge, Mich., [PM40] (Box 2)
    - Engine 1107 and freight train on bridge, Grand Ledge, Mich., [PM41] (Box 2)
    - Engine C, Beaver Island, Mich. 1907, [PM42] (Box 2)
    - Engine 244, [PM43] (Box 2)
    - Tower and station, Grand Junction, Mich., [PM44] (Box 2)
    - Last stand of pine in Kalkaska County, Mich., Dempsey's Siding, Klondike Branch 1904, [PM45] (Box 2)
    - Engine 123 and log train, Klondike Branch, [PM46] (Box 2)
    - Snow plowing, Klondike Branch 1903, [PM47] (Box 2)
    - Engine 128 and mixed train, Spencer, Mich., [PM48] (Box 2)
    - Engine 128 and passenger train, Dempsey's Siding, Mich., Klondike Branch 1903, [PM49] (Box 2)
    - Engine 213, Big Rapids, Mich. 1940, [PM50] (Box 2)
    - Freight train and station, Wellsboro, Ind., [PM51] (Box 2)
    - Engine 423, [PM52] (Box 2)
    - Engine 1213, [PM53] (Box 2)
    - Engine 1229, [PM54] (Box 2)
    - Engine 1410, [PM55] (Box 2)
    - Engine 119 and station, Stratford, Mich., [PM56] (Box 2)
    - Engine 128 on Klondike Branch, [PM57] (Box 2)
    - Engine 485, [PM58] (Box 2)
    - Collision, Salem, Mich. 1907, [PM59-62] (Box 2)
    - Engine 378 and passenger train, Lake Odessa, Mich, [PM63] (Box 2)
    - Engine 158, [PM64] (Box 2)
    - Engine 192, [PM65] (Box 2)
    - Engine 398, [PM66] (Box 2)
    - Engine 1096, [PM67] (Box 2)
    - Engine 1097, [PM68] (Box 2)
    - Engine 1102, [PM69] (Box 2)
    - Engine 1199, [PM70] (Box 2)
    - Engine 1004, [PM71] (Box 2)
    - Engine 3, Windsor, Ont. 1924, [PM72] (Box 2)
    - Engine 4, Sarnia, Ont. 1924, [PM73] (Box 2)
    - Engine 29, Port Huron, Mich. 1924, [PM74] (Box 2)
    - Engine 30, Port Huron, Mich. 1924, [PM75] (Box 2)
    - Engine 810 and train, Walkerville, Ont. 1921, [PM76] (Box 2)
    - Engine 811, Walkerville, Ont. 1920, [PM77] (Box 2)
    - Engine 426, Saginaw, Mich. 1926, [PM78] (Box 2)
    - Engine 477, Muskegon, Mich. 1938, [PM79] (Box 2)
    - Inspection car 2, Grand Rapids, Mich. 1937, [PM80] (Box 2)
    - Station, Mears, Mich., [PM81] (Box 2)
    - Passenger train at station, Shelby, Mich., [PM82] (Box 2)
    - Engine 201 and freight train on High Bridge, Manistee River, Mich. 1909, [PM83] (Box 2)
    - Engine 95 and passenger train on Klondike Branch 1906, [PM84] (Box 2)
    - Station and train, Orleans, Mich., [PM85] (Box 2)
    - Wreck of Engine 425, Stearns, Mich. circa 1912, [PM86] (Box 2)
    - Engine 1222, [PM87] (Box 2)
    - Engine 29, [PM88] (Box 2)
    - Station, Thompsonville, Mich., early 1900s, [PM89] (Box 2)
    - Station, Peacock, Mich., [PM90] (Box 2)
    - Engine 717, [PM91] (Box 2)
    - Engine 154, [PM92] (Box 2)
    - Engines 706 and 32, [PM93] (Box 2)
    - Engine 32 (detail of PM93), [PM94] (Box 2)
    - Station, Grindstone City, Mich. circa 1910, [PM95] (Box 2)
    - Engine 508, [PM96] (Box 2)
    - Wreck near Chase, Mich. 1907, [PM97] (Box 2)
    - Snowplow wreck on Klondike Division 1904, [PM98] (Box 2)
    - Wreck of Engine 92 near Kalkaska, Mich. 1908, [PM99] (Box 2)
    - Wreck of Engines 160 and 210, Mable, Mich. 1910, [PM100] (Box 2)
    - Engine 377 and passenger train, White Cloud, Mich., [PM101] (Box 2)
    - PM and GRI station, Reed City, Mich. 1965, [PM102] (Box 2)
    - Wreck of Engines 160 and 210, Mable, Mich. 1910, [PM103] (Box 2)
    - Station, Thompsonville, Mich. circa 1910, [PM104] (Box 2)
    - Engine C, Beaver Island, Mich. circa 1907, [PM105] (Box 2)
    - Engine 251, [PM106] (Box 2)
    - Wreck on Weidman Branch, early 1900s, [PM107] (Box 2)
    - Snowplow wreck near Shelby, Mich. 1920, [PM108-109] (Box 2)
    - Wreck of Engines 160 and 210, Mable, Mich. 1910, [PM110-113] (Box 2)
    - Three passenger trains at Rapid City, Mich., early 1900s, [PM114] (Box 2)
    - Engine 227 and caboose, [PM115] (Box 2)
    - Building bridge over Cass River, Vassar, Mich. 1903, [PM116] (Box 2)
    - Engine 28 and passenger train at PM and GRI depot, Reed City, Mich., [PM117] (Box 2)
    - Engine 5 and passenger train near Shelby, Mich., [PM118] (Box 2)
    - Snowplow train, Shelby, Mich., [PM119] (Box 2)
    - Depot, Howell, Mich. circa 1910, [PM120] (Box 2)
    - Wreck, St. Louis, Mich. circa 1910, [PM121-122] (Box 2)
    - Engine stuck in snow, Klondike Branch 1904, [PM123] (Box 2)
    - Snowplow wreck, Klondike Branch 1904, [PM124] (Box 2)
    - Engine stuck in snow, [PM125] (Box 2)
    - Engine 1014, [PM126] (Box 2)
    - Engine 68 and wreck, Brighton, Mich. 1910, [PM127-129] (Box 2)
    - Engine 4 and train, St. Louis, Mich., [PM130] (Box 2)
    - Depot, Central Lake, Mich. 1910, [PM131] (Box 2)
    - Snowplow, [PM132] (Box 2)
    - Engine 274, [PM133] (Box 2)
  - Pontiac, Oxford & Northern
    (Code PON)
    - Engine 3 and train, Dryden, Mich., [PON1] (Box 2)
  - Pennsylvania Railroad
    (Code PRR)
    - Engine 925, builder's photo, [PRR1] (Box 2)
    - Engine 658, builder's photo, [PRR2] (Box 2)
    - Engine 19, builder's photo, [PRR3] (Box 2)
    - Engine 48, builder's photo, [PRR4] (Box 2)
    - Engine 949, builder's photo, [PRR5] (Box 2)
    - Engine 173, builder's photo, [PRR6] (Box 2)
    - Engine 6419 Columbus, Ohio 1953, [PRR7] (Box 2)
    - Engine 7345, [PRR8] (Box 2)
    - Engine 6100, [PRR9] (Box 2)
    - Engine 207, [PRR10] (Box 2)
    - Engine 150, [PRR11] (Box 2)
    - Engine 7373, [PRR12] (Box 2)
  - Railway museums
    (Code RM)
    - Rail City, Sandy Pond, N.Y. (Box 2)
    - Huntington & Broad Top Mountain Engine 38 1956, [RM1] (Box 2)
    - Bath & Hammondsport Engine 11 1956, [RM2] (Box 2)
    - Bath & Hammondsport Engine 11 and cars 1956, [RM3] (Box 2)
    - Engines stored 1956, [RM4a-4b] (Box 2)
    - Clark's Dog and Bear Farm, North Woodstock, N.H. (Box 2)
    - Woodstock Lumber Co. Engine 5 1956, [RM5] (Box 2)
    - Beebe River Railroad Engine 6 1956, [RM6] (Box 2)
    - Greenfield Village, Dearborn, Mich. (Box 2)
    - Watertank and station 1958, [RM7] (Box 2)
    - Smith's Creek Station 1958, [RM8] (Box 2)
    - [No entry for RM9], [RM9: unused number] (Box 2)
    - St. Augustine, Fla. (Box 2)
    - St. Johns Railway Engine 7 1960, [RM10] (Box 2)
    - Tweetsie Railroad, Blowing Rock, N.C. (Box 2)
    - Entrance building 1960, [RM11] (Box 2)
    - Station 1960, [RM12] (Box 2)
    - Store building, station and cars 1960, [RM13] (Box 2)
    - Cars 1960, [RM14] (Box 2)
    - Caboose 1960, [RM15] (Box 2)
    - Bradenton, Fla. (Box 2)
    - Locomotive in park 1960, [RM16-17] (Box 2)
    - Chattanooga, Tenn. (Box 2)
    - Western & Atlantic Engine 3, General 1960, [RM18] (Box 2)
    - Yankeetown, Fla. (Box 2)
    - Pat-Mac Engine 3 1961, [RM19-20] (Box 2)
    - Greenfield Village, Dearborn, Mich. (Box 2)
    - Engine General 1963, [RM21-24] (Box 2)
    - Carlton Johnson, Clio, Mich. (Box 2)
    - Engine 11, [RM25-26] (Box 2)
      (no print for RM25)
    - Two Harbors, Minn. (Box 2)
    - Duluth, Missabe & Iron Range Engine 229 1970, [RM27-29] (Box 2)
    - Duluth & Iron Range Engine 3 1970, [RM30-31] (Box 2)
  - St. Clair Tunnel Co.
    (Code SCT)
    - Train approaching tunnel, Port Huron, Mich. 1948, [SCT1] (Box 2)
    - Train leaving tunnel, Port Huron, Mich. 1948, [SCT2] (Box 2)
    - Four-unit electric locomotive (9175, 9151, 9152, 9153) 1948, [SCT3] (Box 2)
    - Trolley installation, GTW yards, Port Huron, Mich. 1948, [SCT4] (Box 2)
    - West end of tunnel, Port Huron, Mich. 1948, [SCT5-6] (Box 2)
    - Approach to west end of tunnel, Port Huron, Mich. 1950, [SCT7] (Box 2)
    - Maintenance cars 1950, [SCT8] (Box 2)
    - Engine 9156, [SCT9] (Box 2)
    - Engine 600, [SCT10] (Box 2)
    - Engine 1304, [SCT11] (Box 2)
  - South Haven & Eastern and Toledo & South Haven
    (Code SH)
    - T&SH Engine 2, South Haven, Mich. 1889, [SH1] (Box 2)
    - SH&E Engine 11 circa 1900, [SH2] (Box 2)
    - SH&E Engine 11 and passenger train circa 1900, [SH3-4] (Box 2)
  - Soo Line
    (Code Soo)
    - Engine 25 and train, Gilchrist, Mich. circa 1938, [Soo1] (Box 2)
    - Engine 18 and caboose, [Soo2] (Box 2)
    - Engine 27, [Soo3] (Box 2)
    - Engine 209, [Soo4] (Box 2)
    - Engine 331, [Soo5] (Box 2)
    - Engine 16 and log train, [Soo6] (Box 2)
  - Street Railroads
    (Code SR)
    - Manistee, Filer City & Eastlake (Box 2)
    - Street car on last trip, [SR1] (Box 2)
    - Lansing City Electric Railway Co. (Box 2)
    - Car 51, [SR2] (Box 2)
    - Commonwealth Ave. Street Railway Co., Boston, Mass. (Box 2)
    - Car 13, [SR3] (Box 2)
    - North Park Railway Co., Rochester, Romeo, and Lake Orion, Mich. (Box 2)
    - Steam dummy and train, [SR4] (Box 2)
    - Fenton & Long Lake, Fenton, Mich. (Box 2)
    - Horse car, Fenton Lake, Mich., [SR5] (Box 2)
    - North Park Railway Co., Rochester, Romeo, and Lake Orion, Mich. (Box 2)
    - Wreck of passenger train circa 1903, [SR6] (Box 2)
    - Reeds Lake Street Railway Co., Grand Rapids, Mich. (Box 2)
    - Engine and train, [SR7] (Box 2)
    - Valley City Street & Cable Railway, Grand Rapids, Mich. (Box 2)
    - Horse and Car 1, [SR8] (Box 2)
    - Fenton & Long Lake, Fenton, Mich. (Box 2)
    - Horse cars at Long Lake (Lake Fenton), early 1900s, [SR9] (Box 2)
    - Detroit & River St. Clair Railway (Box 2)
    - Chicago & Grand Trunk Engine 1009 with steam dummy and Open car 7 circa 1905, [SR10] (Box 2)
    - Fenton & Long Lake, Fenton, Mich. (Box 2)
    - Horse car 4 and horse, [SR11] (Box 2)
  - Saginaw, Tuscola & Huron
    (Code STH)
    - Engine 7 at wreck, [STH1] (Box 2)
    - Engine 10, [STH2-4] (Box 2)
  - Toledo, Ann Arbor & Jackson
    (Code TAJ)
    - Engine 1 and car, Petersburg, Mich. circa 1915, [TAJ1] (Box 2)
    - Engine 2 and train circa 1915, [TAJ2] (Box 2)
    - Passenger train circa 1915, [TAJ3] (Box 2)
  - Thousand Islands Railway
    (Code TI)
    - Engine 500, Gananoque, Ont. 1956, [TI1-2] (Box 2)
    - Station, Gananoque, Ont. 1956, [TI3] (Box 2)
  - Timetables
    (Code TT)
    - Toledo, Ann Arbor & North Michigan and Toledo, Saginaw & Mackinaw 1889, [TT1] (Box 2)
    - Detroit, Bay City & Alpena; Cadillac & Northeastern; Frankfort & Southeastern; and Manistee & North Eastern 1889, [TT2] (Box 2)
    - Toledo & South Haven; Saginaw, Tuscola & Huron; and Pontiac, Oxford & Northern 1889, [TT3] (Box 2)
    - Saginaw Valley & St. Louis and Toledo, Saginaw & Muskegon 1889, [TT4] (Box 2)
  - Toledo Traction Co.
    (Code TTC)
    - Car 403 1898, [TTC1] (Box 2)
  - Toledo & Western
    (Code TW)
    - Engine 405, [TW1] (Box 2)
    - Engine 400, [TW2-4] (Box 2)
    - Engine 400 and caboose 57, [TW5] (Box 2)
    - Snowplow 251, [TW6-7] (Box 2)
    - Baggage car 75, [TW8] (Box 2)
    - Baggage car 76, [TW9] (Box 2)
    - Baggage car 77, [TW10] (Box 2)
    - Passenger car 2, [TW11-12] (Box 2)
    - Passenger car 2 under bridge, [TW13] (Box 2)
    - Passenger car 6, [TW14-15] (Box 2)
    - Passenger car 7, [TW16] (Box 2)
    - Passenger car 8, [TW17-18] (Box 2)
    - Passenger car 30, [TW19] (Box 2)
    - Passenger car 53, [TW20] (Box 2)
    - Passenger car on bridge over LS&MS at Adrian, Mich., [TW21] (Box 2)
    - Car 7, Lyons, Ohio, [TW22] (Box 2)
    - Car 8, Alvordton, Ohio, [TW23] (Box 2)
    - Car 30, Fayette, Ohio, [TW24] (Box 2)
    - Cars, Allen Junction, Ohio, [TW25] (Box 2)
    - Waiting room, Cresceus, Ohio, [TW26] (Box 2)
    - Depot, Blissfield, Mich., [TW27] (Box 2)
    - Street scene, Blissfield, Mich., [TW28] (Box 2)
    - Street scene, Morenci, Mich., [TW29] (Box 2)
    - Carbarn, Sylvania, Ohio, [TW30] (Box 2)
    - New carbodies on flatcars, [TW31] (Box 2)
    - Freight yard, [TW32] (Box 2)
    - Freight house, [TW33] (Box 2)
    - Scene in yard, [TW34] (Box 2)